Come in close.
Closer.
Because the more you think you see,
the easier it'll be to fool you.
Because what is seeing?
You're looking, but what you're really
doing is filtering, interpreting,
searching for meaning.
My job?
To take that most precious ot gifts
you give me, your attention,
and use it against you.
I'm going to flip through this deck.
And I want you to see one card.
Not this one. That's too obvious.
Pay close attention.
That was too fast. I'll do it again.
- Are you ready?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
- Now did you see one?
- Yes.
- Do you have one in mind?
Now, do you see your card here?
No.
That's because you're looking too closely.
And what have I been telling you all night?
The closer you look...
The less you see.
Now look into my eyes.
And sleep. Okay.
And...
If you can get this bill from me,
you can have it.
Go ahead. Take it. Get it.
If you can say your name, you can have it.
All right, just hang out
there, wriggle a sec.
I'm gonna take a little peek under the hood
- of your hubby's brain.
- Oh, no, no, no.
I'm picturing...
Don't tell me. Um...
Of course.
Beach. Cocktails.
Florida?
Look, it was a business trip.
I mean, it is a kind of business.
Maybe the oldest business.
You know what, Honey Bee, let's...
She can't move, Mack.
You're thinking of a woman's name.
J? Jean. Jane. Janet.
Who's Janet?
You know Janet?
It's not your best friend, is it?
- Your sister?
- No, please.
Her sister? Oh, my God.
You weren't away on business.
- You were away on Janet.
- No.
Your wife's sister!
Okay, we need to move over here,
because it seems like
she's a little bit upset right now.
You want this to go away?
- Yes.
- Okay, pull out your wallet.
Come on, get it out.
Do you shake down everybody like this?
No, only the special few.
What is this? Two hundred seem fair?
You know what?
This is a big deal. Let's go $250.
You're a stick-up artist.
Yeah. Of course.
Okay, and sleep!
Now, when I snap my fingers,
you won't remember any of this.
And you, Warren Beatty,
every time you see or even think of Janet,
you're gonna picture me naked.
And that's not a pretty sight.
Yeah.
And... You're wide awake!
Well, we did the best we could,
but some people just
aren't to be hypnotized.
- Oh. I did it wrong?
- Come on, Honey Bee.
- Oh, no, you did it fine.
- Let me buy you dinner.
Look after her.
Just have to hit an ATM first.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I am the next great magician,
and I will give $100
to anyone who can tell me
how this trick is done.
I have an ordinary spoon from Mel's Deli,
right here in Brooklyn.
Check it out.
Now, everyone
please pay very, very close attention.
Because I'm about to
bend this spoon with my mind.
Thank you. Thank you. Pass that around.
- What's this?
- What are you doing, man?
Look at this!
Looks like we got a spoon and a stem.
I've got other tricks.
Or you could give me my 100 bucks.
You said you would.
Nice wallet.
You have a very good eye, sir.
Thanks.
Wallet.
My wallet. My watch!
Stop that guy!
Stop that guy in the leatherjacket!
He's got my wallet!
Whoo! Okay, Los Angeles,
are we ready to end this thing?
Yeah!
When that timer hits zero,
a tank full of flesh-eating piranhas
will fall from above.
A lady has to have handcuffs. Right, girls?
One, two, three!
Yeah!
Help! Stop it!
She's serious! She can't get out!
- Go get some help!
Help, dude!
Get out of the way! Move! Move!
Come on! This is bullshit!
Whoever thought of this is a sick sadist!
Yes!
I am your biggest fan.
I could tell by the way
you're attacking my face right now.
Close the door. Bad apartment building.
- Magician, come here.
- Okay.
Whoa!
- Wait, wait.
- What? What?
How did you do that...
The seven of diamonds
on the side of the tower?
- Yes.
- That's a trade secret.
- Uh-uh.
I'll give you a hint. It involved,
uh, bribing the tower electrician.
- How much?
- Uh, 50 bucks.
- But it's so hard.
- Oh, thank you.
Is it always a seven?
I could do that trick 52 different ways.
Can you do 52 different tricks on me?
I'll see what I can do.
Ooh! Magic man!
Ah! I love your shampoo.
- Whoa! Hold up.
- What?
You need to leave.
Are you kidding me?
Oh, my God, this is so embarrassing.
Is this what you do?
Some kind of sick trick you do to women?
"45 East Evan Street."
Don't worry about it. I'll call you.
You don't have my number.
I'm magic. I'll find it. Have a good night.
Oh, you are such an asshole.
I'm going to go with her.
Go. I got your back. I'll be right here.
Go ahead!
That's on you, Fuller.
Let's go, let's go! Now, now, now!
Daniel?
Hey!
Henley.
Danny? Hey.
- Ah. You got a card, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
No, no, no, it's good for you. Congratulations.
All right, so here's what I'm gonna do,
I'm gonna go inside.
I'm gonna scope the place out.
You wait out here. I will come back
and get you, okay? Do not come in.
Hey, Danny! I'm not your assistant anymore.
Nice hair.
So, um, actually,
what have you been up to?
I think you know exactly
what I've been up to, Danny.
I saw all your anonymous
posting on my website.
You have a website. That's good.
Good for you. Get the word out.
- Oh.
- Uh...
Okay.
So apparently none of us
was the only one chosen.
Let me be the first one
to kick my ego to the curb.
Yeah. Excuse me.
- Door's locked.
- Is it? I'll check.
You. Now, hold it, don't tell me. Uh...
Helen? No, no.
Henley.
It's on your coffee cup.
Thanks for keeping me honest.
That wasn't mentalism, by the way.
It was just an observation.
Second observation, you are beautiful.
Thank you.
That's good. That's very nice.
Very well-polished. Nice bit.
J. Daniel Atlas. Nice to meet you.
Very nice. I know who you are
and I just want to say that
I'm not interested in you doing
your mentalism thing on us.
Especially when we don't know
who brought us here or even if it's real.
Shh! Hold on, I'm sensing...
I'm sensing you
are a control freak.
I'm sorry, have we met before?
It doesn't take a mentalist
to figure that out.
You are a control freak.
Well, I take that as a compliment.
Only he would take it as a compliment.
Okay, great. Good. Another compliment.
Okay. So that's why
you're no longer a couple.
A couple? No, no.
We were never a couple.
He used to saw me in half.
She was a very good assistant.
But I was too fat for Danny.
No. I said that one time
because of the trap door.
- There were specs.
- You built it this size.
No one could fit through there. No one.
- Rebecca fit through.
- Ah...
Rebecca fit for years.
Do you know how hard it is to stay
in those tiny little costumes?
No. I'm the main attraction.
Okay. So he never made you feel special.
And, trust me, you deserve
to be made to feel special.
That's a really nice story.
Hope you guys enjoy each other's company.
No way.
J. Daniel Atlas?
Dude, I've seen everything
that you have ever done.
You're like...
I idolize you. Seriously.
From a true fan. It's so nice to meet you.
I'm Jack, by the way.
Question. Did you get one of these?
Yeah. Death.
The High Priestess.
I'm the Lover.
Three minutes.
Hermit.
So, what are we...
Are we waiting for someone?
- Why are we just...
- The door's locked.
Oh, no, nothing's ever locked.
Hmm.
What is this place?
- Ugh!
- Oh!
Wow. Thought my apartment was nasty.
Man, it's freezing in here.
What's that?
I don't know.
What's it say?
"Now you don't."
"A rose by any other name..."
Guys, what's happening?
Whoa.
Look at that.
It's gas!
Relax. Just dry ice.
Cool.
Wait. What do you think this is all about?
Hang on. Hang on.
I got nothin'.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you for the delay.
I'm just trying to create
the space for wisdom.
Okay, so you're like Buddha,
if he wasn't so enlightened.
And you're like Jesus,
if he was arrogant
and all of his miracles were fake.
Okay, lovebirds, get a room.
Danny, be honest. Did you do this?
No. Wait, did you?
I wish.
Why didn't anyone ask me if I did it?
Oh, great.
Electricity is out.
Well, let's check.
Whoa.
Blueprints.
They're incredible.
Who do you think did this?
I don't know, but I
really want to meet them.
It's a show.
Wow.
Merritt McKinney,
Daniel Atlas,
Henley Reeves,
Jack Wilder.
Arthur Tress/er and the MGM Grand
proudly presents
The Four Horsemen.
Thank you.
Tonight we would like to try something
that will, well, set us a bit apart.
For our final trick,
we're gonna do something never before
seen on a Las Vegas stage.
Or any stage for that matter.
Ladies and gentlemen,
tonight
we are going to rob a bank.
That's a lot of excitement for a crime.
I'm getting excited.
What about you, people?
One, two, three!
Sorry, sir. There's absolutely no recording
allowed during the performance.
Oh, yeah, yeah, sure, of course.
- Let me just put this away.
Actually, I need to take that.
After the show, I can come
and give it back to you.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Now, please, please, settle down.
Now who here has a bank
they would like us to rob?
That's a lot of people with a vendetta.
So we'll choose one at random then.
My associates will make sure
it's random. Right?
Thank you, Merritt.
We are looking at row number 5.
Where is that?
And Henley, could I please
have a random seat number?
Oh. Lucky number 13.
- B-5-13. Where are you?
Sir, please, stand up.
Ah, there you are. Hi.
Could you just confirm for me that this
is, in fact, your seat? B-5-13.
Yes.
Okay. Wonderful.
Now, could you please tell us
your name and the name of your bank?
Well, my name is Etienne Forcier.
And my bank, it's Credit
Republicain de Paris.
French. Okay. Uh...
We were hoping for something
a little more local,
a kind of mom-and-pop
credit union with no security.
But that's fine. A promise is a promise.
Could you please come up to the stage
- and we'll rob your bank.
And while he does that...
There is someone here tonight
without whom we would just be
four magicians working the circuit,
trying to get...
Well, actually, trying to get here.
You probably know this man,
if not from one of the many, many
companies he puts his name on.
He is our friend. He is our benefactor.
Mr. Arthur Tressier.
Please, stand up, Art. Please, stand up.
The only man here with
the Queen's cell phone number.
Actually, please, stay standing, Art.
I want to say that when we came
to Mr. Tressier,
we promised that, as a unit, we could
become the biggest name in magic.
So we wanted to say, "Thank you."
And by the way, Art,
you notice on the sign out front,
we made sure we put your name on top.
If you turn out to be as good
as you think you are, dear girl,
that won't be necessary much longer.
We haven't done our closer yet.
- Why don't you watch it
and then you can decide for yourself.
Ladies and gentlemen, Arthur Tressier!
Thank you.
And, of course, once again,
the Cardinal of Clairvoyance,
Merritt McKinney.
Etienne, what Jack
is bringing to the stage now,
is what we in the magic world
call a teleportation helmet.
You will need to wear this, as it will allow
you to literally fold through space and time
to your bank in the...
8th?
- 9th arrondissement.
- Yeah.
Now, once you are there, we will be able
to speak with you through this helmet.
- Now if... Ah!
- Ow.
- Oh, my God, that's beautiful.
It has the added attraction of being
very stylish.
It's about time the French learned
from America on that subject.
Is that a beautiful piece of headgear?
- Thank you. Thank you...
- It is.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Mais oui. Mais oui.
But before you go anywhere,
could you please, pick a card, any card.
Not that card. Oh!
No, that's an old American joke.
You can take that one.
Okay. This one?
Show it to your friends in Section B.
But not to us.
Okay, great.
Now if you could just sign your name there.
- Yes.
- In English, if possible.
- That's good.
- Thanks.
Put it in your pocket.
And now for one tiny detail.
Now, Etienne, let's step into
this cockamamie contraption.
And I'll step off of it. Bonne chance.
It's 11:50 p.m. here in Vegas.
That's 8:50 a.m. in Paris.
Your bank opens in less than 10 minutes.
One,
two...
Three.
What the fuck?
- Wow! Etienne?
- Whoa. Etienne?
It wasn't supposed to happen
like that, was it?
Etienne?
I liked that little French guy.
Where did he go?
Wait, there he is.
No, no, no, no, please, please, please.
This is Daniel Atlas. Can you hear me?
- Etienne? Are you okay?
- Yes.
Perfect. What do you see in there?
Money.
Is this real?
Yes. Looks like three million or so
Euros' worth.
Okay, now, here's what
we're gonna need you to do.
I want you to take the card that you signed
out of your pocket.
And I want you to take the ticket stub
from tonight's show
and I want you to put it right there
in the middle of the money.
Now drop it.
Now, on the side of your helmet
you should feel a button.
Don't press it just yet.
That button activates an air duct
that connects Paris to Las Vegas.
Okay, good. Now you can press it.
All right, now, Etienne, hold on tight.
You might feel a bit of a vacuum.
Whoo!
Oh. Wait a second.
- Huh.
Oh, merde.
Thank you, Etienne. Thank you, everyone!
We are The Four Horsemen.
- And good night!
- Good night!
Hold up here.
Dylan Rhodes.
What? I don't think I heard you correctly.
Did you say magicians?
Yeah, Dylan, magicians.
Where are you now?
I'm at Aria.
I'm heading up there to grab 'em now.
FBI! Hands where I can see them.
Let's go. Get 'em up. Come on.
Uno minute.
Let's go. Get 'em up.
Put the book down.
Okay. You got me.
- Freeze! Hands in the air!
- Oh, my!
Do one of you guys
mind giving us a hand with our bags?
Let's go.
Boss, please tell me this is a joke.
I just got Willy Mears
to finger Paulie Attanasio.
I'm a month, two tops,
away from blowing this whole thing open.
- Get Turkelson.
- He's in Atlantic City.
What about Cowan? Look at him.
He's just sitting there on his ass.
Hilarious, Rhodes.
I love you.
Asshole.
I don't have time for this magic crap.
This crap just pulled
three million Euro out of a Parisian bank.
- That's how much they got?
- Yeah.
Actually, 3.2.
- Who is she?
Who are you?
Alma Dray from Interpol.
I'll be working the investigation with you.
You gotta be kidding me.
It's bad enough they got me chasing down
David Copperfield and Friends.
Now I'm being saddled with,
no offense, with Interpol?
I look forward to working
with you, too, Agent Rhodes.
I'm sorry. I don't think I'm gonna
need your help on this. Okay?
- Where's the French guy?
- I already spoke to him.
Oh, you did?
You spoke to my witness before me?
Your witness?
I thought you didn't want the case.
Besides, he's useless.
Oh, really? Why is that?
Because he believes their magic was real.
Oh, he believes the magic was real?
You're right, he probably is useless.
Is it okay with Interpol
if we talk to him, too?
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
I have never stolen a
thing in my life, okay?
I tried to give the money back,
but they won't take it.
Okay, okay, okay,
let's just say you robbed a bank.
I did.
Fine. Fantastic. You did.
But since I'm new to this,
can you explain to me how you went
from Las Vegas to Paris in three seconds?
With the teleportation helmet.
Okay, what the hell is going on here?
He was hypnotized during the show.
I told you, he's useless.
Okay, I'll deal with you when I'm done
with this other bullshit.
Hey!
During the show,
half the audience was hypnotized
to believe they were in the Philharmonic.
I guess that "bullshit"
was the trigger word.
Okay. Hey, hey. Écoutez.
Etienne, come on down from there.
You're not in the Philharmonic.
- How do you say "stop" in French?
- Stop.
Tell him to stop.
No, I can't. You just have to
let him finish his movement.
Okay, I need a time-out.
Too many French people in one room.
- Agent Rhodes!
- Huh?
I'm ordered by my bosses
to provide a report.
And until we have one, I'm
here, like it or not.
So we can work together,
or you can continue to follow behind
asking the same exact questions I'm asking.
It's up to you.
Hmm.
I'm not finished.
I just flew 12 hours,
after what was already a long day.
And I do not handle jet lag well.
So if you want to see who can be grumpier,
- I promise you, you will lose.
- Hmm.
Mm-hmm. Fine. So which one of these idiots
do you want to talk to first?
Him?
Dylan, for the record,
mentalism has never actually
been proven to be accurate.
Okay.
That is to say, that it's not a science.
It's more for entertainment.
All right.
Just don't believe everything the guy says.
That's all.
Please convey my deepest apologies
to your colleague out there.
I'm really sorry about this
whole Tranny Tuesday thing.
I was out of line.
Tranny Tuesday?
Well, it's an arrangement
he and his wife have.
Or might not have, if you believe
everything Agent Fuller
is saying to be correct.
But isn't there a proud tradition
in the FBI of men wearing dresses?
No shame, Agent Fuller. No shame.
I'm just having fun.
Was this your card? No.
See, I knew you weren't
a queen of hearts lady,
and I respect that.
The trick usually works better
when I'm not strapped in here,
but I understand protocol.
Okay, okay.
So, if you had nothing to do with it,
then how did
the playing card get into the vault?
Oh, yes. That would be...
What do the kids call it these days?
Oh, yes, that's right. Magic.
Just answer the question, okay, smartass.
All right. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
You can keep that. Don't share it with him.
It says here you are a mentalist.
- Hmm.
- What exactly is mentalism?
Tricks, mostly. Um, some science.
Targeted guessing
might be a most apt description.
Along with some intuition
and the occasional...
Voices in my head.
Says here you were fairly
famous at one point.
Mm-hmm.
You can
even hypnotize people over the phone.
Some big tours
around the U.S. for a few years,
- two TV specials.
- Glory days.
Then your brother/manager disappeared
with all your hard-earned money.
Did your research, did you?
IRS audit. Back taxes.
You've had a long hard slog back into the
limelight, haven't you, Mr. McKinney?
Yes, indeed, it has. And I do appreciate
that trip down Memory Lane.
As far as I understand it,
when the man from Paris
put on the magical helmet...
Listen to me.
If you didn't rob that bank,
then you knew about it.
Which makes you an accomplice.
So if you wanna walk out of here today,
I'd suggest you start...