A famous man once said,
"We create our own demons."
Who said that?
What does that even mean?
Doesn't matter.
I said it because he said it.
So, now, he was famous
and it's basically getting said
by two well-known guys.
I don't, uh...
I'm going to start again.
Let's track this from the beginning.
♪ Yo listen up here's a story
♪ About a little guy that
lives in a blue world
♪ And all day and all night
and everything he sees
♪ Is just blue like him
inside and outside
♪ Blue is his house
with a blue little window
♪ And a blue Corvette
♪ And everything is blue
for him and himself
♪ And everybody around
♪ 'Cause he ain't got nobody... ♪
Half hour till the ball drops.
- Hey, do you wanna...
- Tony Stark?
- Great speech, man!
- I got you, pal.
I gave a speech? How was it?
- Edifying.
- Unintelligible.
- Really?
- Mmm-hmm.
It's my favourite kind.
A winning combo.
- Where are we going?
- Uh, to town, on each other.
Probably back in your room
because I also want to
see your research.
Okay, you can see my research,
but that's...
I'm not gonna show you my "town."
Mr Stark.
Ho Yinsen.
Ah, I finally met a man called "Ho."
- Come here.
I would like to
introduce you to our guest, Dr Wu.
- Oh, this guy. Hey.
- Mr Stark.
- You're a heart doctor.
She's going to need
a cardiologist after I...
- Bye.
- Perhaps another time?
It started in
Bern, Switzerland. 1999.
- The old days.
- Mr Stark!
I never thought they
would come back to bite me.
Why would they?
Oh, wow! Hey, Tony!
Aldrich Killian.
I'm a big fan of your work.
- My work?
- Who isn't? He means me.
Well, of course, but, Ms Hansen,
my organisation's been tracking
your research since year two of MIT.
Yeah, we're full.
Oh, wow, he made it.
He made the cut.
What floor you going to, pal?
Well, now, that is
an appropriate question.
The ground floor, actually,
of a proposal
I'm putting together myself.
It's a privately funded think tank
called Advanced Idea Mechanics.
- Uh...
- She'll take both.
One to throw away and one to not call.
"Advanced Idea Mechanics"
or "AIM," for short. Do you get it?
- I see that, because it's on your T-shirt.
- Aw!
Ladies, follow the mullet. Ladies first.
Thank you, I'll call you.
I'm titillated by the notion
of working with you.
- Yeah?
- I'll ditch these clowns.
I'll see you up
on the roof in five minutes.
Just gonna try
and get my beak wet real quick.
You know what I'm talking about?
I'll see you up there.
Damn betcha.
Come on!
I thought that was just a theory.
Well, it was.
If I'm right, we can access the area
of the brain
- that governs repair...
- Wow.
...and chemically recode it.
That's incredible. Essentially,
you're hacking into the genetic...
...operating system...
- ...of a living organism.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
- Wow.
Is that...
Can you...
- What?
- Can you not touch my plant?
It's not...
She doesn't like it. She prefers...
She's not like the others.
Come on. Let's go in the bedroom.
- Happy...
- Hmm. That's cute...
Leave her ficus alone.
Because...
And, no, seriously, don't.
And you're starting with plants.
- For now, yeah.
- Huh.
I'm calling it EXTREMIS.
- Well, it's...
- Human application.
Exactly, exactly.
- Dendritic revitalisation.
- It's revolutionary.
- Disease prevention...
- Change the world.
...even limb regrowth.
You're the most gifted woman
I've ever met.
Wow.
- In Switzerland.
- Hmm. That's better.
- Aw, you're seeing things.
- This week.
You almost
bought it, didn't you?
This is what I'm talking about,
the glitch.
Have you checked
the telomerase algorithm?
- The what?
- Down!
Stay down! Stay down, boss.
- We're good.
- Stay down.
You... You're...
You're right on me. I made it.
What the hell was that?
- What was that?
- It's a glitch in my work. It's...
She was just talking about it.
Glitches happen.
It's not Y2K.
- Hey! Happy New Year!
- Happy New Year.
All right.
I'll see you in the morning. Good night.
- You good?
- Yeah.
- I'll be right outside.
- Okay, cool.
So, why am I telling you this?
Because I had just created demons
and I didn't even know it.
- Yeah, those were good times.
Then I moved on.
After a brief soirée in an Afghan cave,
I said goodbye to the party scene.
I forgot that night in Switzerland.
These days, I'm a changed man.
Forty-six.
- I'm different now.
I'm... Well...
- Forty-seven.
- You know who I am.
Ow!
Sir, please may I request
just a few hours to calibrate...
No. Forty-eight.
Micro-repeater
implanting sequence complete.
As you wish, sir.
I've also prepared a safety briefing
for you to entirely ignore.
Which I will.
All right, let's do this.
Hi, DUM-E.
How did you get that cap on your head?
You earned it.
Hey. Hey!
What are you doing out of the corner?
You know what you did.
Blood on my mat. Handle it.
Sir, may I remind you that you've been
awake for nearly 72 hours?
Focus up, ladies.
Good evening,
and welcome to the birthing suite.
I am pleased to announce
the imminent arrival
of your bouncing,
bad-ass baby brother.
Start tight and then go wide.
Stamp date and time.
Mark 42. Autonomous
prehensile propulsion suit test.
Initialise sequence.
Jarvis, drop my needle.
♪ Dashing through the snow
♪ In a one horse open sleigh
♪ O'er the fields we go
♪ Laughing all the way
♪ Bells on bob tails ring
Crap.
♪ Oh, what fun it is to sing
♪ A sleighing song tonight
♪ Jingle bells, jingle bells
♪ Jingle all the way
♪ Oh, what fun it is to ride
♪ In a one horse open sleigh ♪
All right, I think we got this.
Send them all.
Probably a little fast.
Slow it down.
- Slow it down just a...
...little bit.
Cool it, will you, Jarvis?
Come on. I ain't scared of you.
I'm the best.
As always, sir, a great pleasure
watching you work.
I guess 72 hours is a long time
between siestas.
I didn't think it could get any worse.
Then I had to go and turn on the TV.
That's when he happened.
Some people
call me a terrorist.
I consider myself a teacher.
America.
Ready for another lesson?
In 1864, in Sand Creek, Colorado,
the US military waited
until the friendly Cheyenne braves
had all gone hunting.
Waited to attack and slaughter
the families left behind
and claim their land.
39 hours ago,
the Ali AI Salem Air Base in Kuwait
was attacked.
I... I... I did that.
A quaint military church
filled with wives and children,
of course.
The soldiers were out on manoeuvres.
The braves were away.
President Ems.
You continue to resist my attempts
to educate you, sir.
And now you've missed me again.
You know who I am.
You don't know where I am.
And you'll never see me coming.
Now that we seem to be back,
let's recap some
of the frightening developments...
American airwaves were hijacked...
The nation remains on high alert.
All attempts to find the Mandarin
have so far proved unsuccessful.
Central to my administration's
response to this terrorist event
is a newly minted resource.
I know him
as Colonel James Rhodes.
The American people
will soon know him
as the tron Patriot.
And how is President Ems responding?
By taking the guy
they call War Machine
and giving him a paint job.
The same suit,
but painted red, white and blue.
Look at that. And they also
renamed him, "Iron Patriot."
You know,
just in case the paint was too subtle.
It tested well with focus groups,
all right?
"I am Iron Patriot!" It sucks.
Listen. "War Machine"
was a little too aggressive.
All right?
This sends a better message.
So, what's really going on?
With the Mandarin.
Seriously, can we talk about this guy?
It's classified information, Tony.
Okay, there have been nine bombings.
- Nine.
- The public only knows about three.
But here's the thing,
nobody can ID a device.
There's no bomb casings.
You know I can help.
Just ask.
I got a ton of new tech.
I got a prehensile suit.
I got bomb disposal.
It catches explosions in mid-air.
When's the last time
you got a good night's sleep?
Einstein slept three hours a year.
Look what he did.
People are concerned about you, Tony.
I'm concerned about you.
You're going to come at me like that?
No, look, I'm not trying to be a dick...
...tator.
Do you mind signing my drawing?
- If Richard doesn't mind.
Are you all right with this, Dick?
Yeah. Fine with me.
- What's your name?
- Erin.
I loved you in A Christmas Story,
by the way.
Listen, the Pentagon is scared.
After New York, aliens... Come on.
They need to look strong.
Stopping the Mandarin is a priority,
but it's not...
- it's not superhero business.
- No, it's not, quite frankly.
- I get it.
- It's American business.
That's why I said I got it.
- Are you okay?
I broke the crayon.
Are you okay, Mr Stark?
Take it easy. Tony.
How did you
get out of the wormhole?
- Wait a minute. Tony!
- What did you say?
- Tony.
Sorry.
I'm just checking on the suit.
Okay.
Check the heart.
Is it the brain?
No sign of cardiac anomaly
or unusual brain activity.
Okay, so I was poisoned?
My diagnosis is that you've
experienced a severe anxiety attack.
- Me?
Come on, man, this isn't a good look.
Open up.
Sorry, I gotta split.
Badge.
- Badge.
Come on, badge.
Badge, guys.
I put a memo in the toilet. Come on.
Tony has got them in his basement.
They're wearing party hats.
- This is an asset that we can put to use.
- Uh-huh.
So, you're suggesting that I replace
the entire janitorial staff with robots.
- Thank you.
- What I'm saying is that
the human element of human resources
is our biggest point of vulnerability.
We should start
phasing it out immediately.
- What?
- Excuse me, Bambi,
- you should be wearing...
- Did you just say that?
- Security? Yes?
- Happy? Okay.
I am thrilled that you are now
the Head of Security. Okay?
- It is the perfect position for you.
- Thank you.
- However...
- I do appreciate it.
- ...since you've taken the post...
- You don't have to thank me.
...we've had a rise in staff complaints
of 300%.
Thank you.
It's not a compliment.
It's not...
It is a compliment.
Clearly, somebody's
trying to hide something.
- I... Yes.
- Excuse me.
Ms Potts, your 4:00 is here.
- Thank you.
Did you clear this 4: -00 with me?
Happy, we'll talk about this later,
but right now, I have to go deal with
this very annoying thing.
How so?
I used to work with him
and he used to ask me out all the time,
so it's a little awkward.
I don't like the sound of that.
Pepper.
Killian?
You look great.
You look really great.
God, you look great.
What on earth have you been doing?
Nothing fancy.
Just five years in the hands
of physical therapists.
And please, call me Aldrich.