I took your advice,
it was good advice,
thank you
You look sick,
evertyhing ok?
Sean,
Sean!
Hey
Anyway listen I wanted to tell you, the only
reason why I canceled..
He calls three times a day.
I hear more from him now, than I did when we were together.
What is it with guys?
I gave notice.
-Notice?-
May I see your ticket?
-I ehh...
Hey
You are acting really strange this morning,
are you ok?
Are we gonna make up the 10 Minutes?
-We gonna try, Sir.-
Hey, grandpa, what the heck was they delay back there?
I just purge the tickets, Sir.
-I'd punch your face-
Sean
did I do something?
Look, I can see, that you think you know
me but I dont know who you are
My name ist Captain Colter Stevens
I fly Helicopeters for the US-Army in Afghanistan
Sean, that's ....
-Sean?-
I feel sick.
Careful!
-Oh, I am sorry!-
Right, let me help you.
No, it's ok.
Hey Mister..Hey!
You dropped this!
-Thanks!-
What is that?
-Chicago-
"All on board, door are closing"
"This is a chicago-down train"
You ok there, captain?
Did you see that?
You kinda freak me out.
No, no, no.
"Sean Fentress
Teacher"
Oh my...
Are you all right?
-I don't know, what's going on-
Talk to me shawn!
-I don't know who shawn is, and I don't
know who you are!-
Ok we can get off at the next stop
and forget whatever is going on here.
This papers doesn't belong to me.
Look at me,
everything is gonna be ok!
Captain Stevens, this is beleagured castle
Captain Stevens, this is beleagured Castle
acknowledge transmission!
Captain Stevens, do you copy?
Where am I?
You are with (operation) "Beleagured Castle"
Are you functional?
I am dizzy. Was there a drop in height?
Adjusting your orientation.
Can you report it this time?
What is this ?
What is this?
Where....who I am talking to?
Captain report what you saw.
I don't understand it
-Where were you, before you were talking to me?-
There was an explosion.
-Coming from where?-
Some confusion is perfectly normal at this stage, Captain.
Do you have a visual signal?
Who are you?
You already have that information captain.
-I do?-
Recall my name.
We'll rebuild the pattern. Try to focus.
I...was on a misson
I was flying...
And then I woke up on a train.
Now I am here.
I need to be briefed.
What unit is this?
You are with "Beleagured Castle".
- Who? -
Let's start part 1 of memory pattern -
-What is "beleaguared castle?"-
The exercises will assist you.
Part1: This is a following passage
Lilly awoke in an evening dress and an opera cloak
in her hand were 5 play cards
-this is a joke?-
They were:
Queen Spade, 4 clubs
9 of clubs,
3 at heart, 9 at heart
Is this a red flag exercise?
End of part 1.
Part2
The following is a recording of a western screetch-owl
End of part 2. End of pattern.
Acknowledge
Acknowledge end of pattern.
Stand by to initiate pattern recall?
Go for pattern recall.
Arrange the 5 playing cards in order a descending value irrespective of their suit.
Queen, two nines, four and a three
-That is correct-
The passage I read contained mention of a woman's name.
What was that name?
Her name is Lilly.
That's correct
Recall my name.
Goodwin, your name is goodwin, Captain.
That is correct, welcome back, captain.
Ma'm, I need to talk to my father.
Has anybody been notified that I am state-side?
Who bombed the train, captain?
What?
-Who bombed the train?-
A woman kept calling me "Sean".
That is incidental
Think captain, remember back.
Who bombed the train?
I don't know who bombed the god damn train.
Then go back and try again.
-Back where?-
You will have 8 minutes, same as last time.
No, No, no more bullshit semi-tests.
I need to know, where I am, what is the location and condition of my crew.
Does anybody know, that I am stateside?
You are obligated to give me this information!
-Start with the bomb!-
Where is it and what does it look like.
What kind of explosive, how is it detonated.
-Right, right-
Find the bomb and you'll find the bomber.
-Find the bomb....wait nooo!-
I took your advice, it was good advice. Thank you.
Yeah, its good.
And I signed to a law-course.
Next thing you know, I'll be moving to india to find myself.
Laws....
Know any good Gurus?
On your shoe...
So what do you think, am I on the right track?
It's the same train but it's different.
Deep. I hope it's different.
I feel the same way.
What?
-Go ahead-
What is with guys, everything is beatiful in retrospect.
This looks so real.
You know, I think it'll be really good for me to get away from him
as far as possible
Unbelieveable details.
-Ticket-
May I see your ticket?
Thanks.
The doer wouldn't place you right of me.
You are a pretty girl. a distraction.
A "distraction"?
-Every simulator has one-
Hey are we gonna make up the two minutes?
-We are gonna try-
Are you talking about Brian?
-Hey Grandpapa-
what the heck was the delay back there?
What you late for?
You seem concerned about the time.
What are you late for?
I have be at a festival with assholes...like you!
Oh thats funny. Who are you, a comedian?
Yea, he is a...
comedian
Sit down, freak.
Freak
Thats the guy. He won 3th place in america got talent.
He got arrested two times for dui.
We talked about him.
-Thank you-
-You welcome-
You are welcome.
"Mainbruck station"
Damn it!
Ah, I am sorry.
Hey Mr., hey
You dropped it.
-Thanks-
"All aboard, doors are closing"
Explosion came from behind me.
What's with you ?
I don't have time to talk to you right now
I got time for you
Next stop : "Chicago, Union-Station"
Holy shit...
Goodwin, you have to tell me, how to disarm this.
Ehmm...should I unplug it?
Or do you want me to just leave it?
Ok, ehmm
I am just gonna leave it.
ok?
"Sean Fentress,
Teacher"
Ladies and Gentleman, Transit Security
No, you're not.
We have a classified security-breach and I want you turn off
your personal electronic devices till we reach another station
That means laptops
Cellphones
Cellphones Sir!
Thank your very much.
Pagers, anything electronic.
It's a precautionary measure, nothing to worry about.
So which is it, security breach or precautionary measure.
Sir!
Is there a problem, Sir?
-I am in the middle of a very big deal-
Sean?
I need you to turn that off.
Why you don't show my your id again?
Sean!
Turn it off!
What's your problem, asshole?
Hey!
Sean, what are you doing ?
Not a good idea m'am.
I think , you broke his jaw.
It's ok, he is not any more real than you are.
I am not real?
How about next time you drive to work !
There's not gonna be a next time.
stabilized?
Lower your pulse.
Did you find the bomb?
-Yes-
There is a strange hydraulic fluid all over the floor.
It's not a concern, captain.
Tell me about the bomb.
Where is that man? I saw a guy with a crutch on my monitor.
He looks like he is in charge, I wonna talk to him.
-Thats irrelevant captain-
I wonna talk to your commanding officer!
-You can talk to him upon completion of your mission-
My mission is in Afghanistan, where my unit is.
I flew two god damn missions yesterday.
You've been with us for 2 months.
Did you id the bomber?
-No, where is my unit?-
And under who's leadership is this simulation?
Captain, this is not a simulation. Lives are depending on you.
What lives?
What do you remember about the bomb?
Tell me about the detonator.
No, what lives, what you are talking about?
I need to be briefed!
Sir, I need to give him something.
-That's fine, go ahead-
Get ready to sent him back out.
At 7:48 this morning, a bomb exploded in a commuter train outside of chicago, killing
everyone on board.
and thats the train, you been on.
No no, I am right here,
you are talking to me.. right now!
A man named Sean Fentress was on that train.
In a sense....he is now you.
Every second spend, explaining things puts more innocents  civilians at risk.
This makes no sense.
The train explosion was the first attack of a series.
There are going to be more.
Now, did you find the bomb?
In the restroom, ventilation-panel above the sink.
cellphone-detonator.
Are we done?
Eh, no no. But thats good, thats very very good, captain.
good.
Our records show, that 1812 calls ended at the moment of the explosion.
52 of those calls were received by cell tower nearby and reversed to the train. So one of those calls was made by our bomber.
Do you remember a freight train passing by, just before the explosion?
Yes.
The explosion was timed to engulf the passing freight train
which means, the bomber had be watching both trains
when the call was made.
52 callers.... one of those is our bomber.
I want you to concentrate on the passengers in your car.
Get to know them, narrow suspectpool.
Look for ones, who seem quite or withdrawn, who seem nervous.
As always, you have 8 minutes.
8 minutes, and I blow up again?
Yes
I need you to discipline yourself on this next path.
Perform only the task, that we assign you.
Everything else is irrelevant.
Start the sequence.
...is my father even...
I took your advice...
it was very good advice
You're kinda quite today?
-Just got a lot on my mind.-
Carefull !
Oops
Oh, I am so sorry
-Don't worry about it-
That's very kind of you.
You're very decent.
Thank you.
And real.
-Ticket!-
How you doing today?
-good-
Anything unusual?
-Ehmm no-
I mean behavior on the train.
Is anything or anybody seems strange to you?
You look strange.
How about you,
does anybody looks suspicious?
Are you drunk or something?
-Come here-
For a second.
come on.
Just think of it as a game.
-A game?-
They are all so utterly normal, Sean.
That's what so terrifying about them.
Maybe there is a team network.
The sleeping giant coache with the ministry and the comedian.
Don't forget the student, he is expendable.
But they are all controlled by the conductor.
Standing there like a king and demanding tickets.
You are funny.
-Damn it-
What about that guy?
-Deposition-
And the woman who is sitting cross him?
Hair appointment, every monday, you know this.
You know this people better than me.
And the guy behind her?
He's late for an audition, right?
Or audition to the court
he got caught driving drunk twice.
-Hey, hows the signal in here?-
Good
Is teaching not stimulating enough for you anymore, Sherlock?
Oh oh, the toilet ist sure jammed now.
-Did anyone else come out of the bathroom?-
Well, I saw you coming out of there.
-Me?
Yes.
-No-
Me?
-Hey Mr.-
Hold on a second.
What's in here.
A broken phone.
What is this.
Coffee with Christina.
Christina?
-Yeah-
Excuse me.
Hey,  hey come with me.
-This isn't our stop!-
come on, let's take a walk.
-We don't get off here.-
I don't know, just be spontaneaous.
-You start freaking me out-
I know this sounds a bit weird
but I have a really bad feeling about this train
and that we should get off, ok?
Just get your stuff.
Doors are closing.
Come on, come with me.
So what now?
-Wait here, I will be right back!-
Ready for coffee now?
Oh sorry, ah yea yea,
just one more second, ok?
Oh for god's sake.
Feeling Sick?
Motion sickness, I get it all the time.
Excuse...
Are you following me?
-Can I borrow your phone?-
No, I don't have one.
Sure?
-Yea, I am sure-
Why you dont leave me alone please?
Or I call the police.
With what?
I thought, you didn't have a phone.
You know, you have no right....
Gimme my bag back.
Are you crazy
Sean!
-Get back!-
Sean, what's going on?
Sean
It wasn't you.
-What the hell is wrong with you?
Are you insane?
-No-
Where is it???
-Get away from me please!-
Sean, Sean
get off!
Listen to me, get up!
Sean
-Gimme your hand, get off the track-
Goodwin
Come on, do you here me?
Captain Stevens, this is beleaguared castle
do you copy? please respond
It's freezying here, whats going on.
What's that
He is in trouble.
I think the oxygen just went out.
Goodwin
Goodwin!
Find a way to get through to him.
What is it?
What's going on?
It's not the tertiary cooling ether.
Just keep sending strings up,
maybe he hooks on to something.
It's hard to tell what exactly he is going through.
Sir...
-Lord, please-
It's not a lot we can do from here.
If nothing changes, who much time do we have?
-Some-
and not long
Lilly awoke in an evening dress and an opera cloak,
she had 5 playing cards in her hand...
Goodwin, you out there?
Goodwin, who is Goodwin.
-This is Captain Stevens, do you copy-
Captain Stevens?
The capsule lost power
The capsule?
Is that where you are now, in a capsule?
You should know, who are you?
-Let me get captain Goodwin for you-
You invented this thing, right?
I did.
-Are you in command here ?-
I am... were you able to locate information we need,
captain?
Negative Sir, I was unable to find the bomber, but I did safe her.
A passenger on the train.
I got her off safely, a woman
Captain, it's gonna be contra-prodactive for you to safe anyone on the train. They're outside the mission.
Well, she survived.
And maybe this will work with the rest too.
She survived, but only inside of the source code.
None of them will be safe.
What is this source code?
Its quantum mechanics parabolic calculus.
It's very complicated.
Try me!
Fine.
When a light blub turned off, there is an afterglow, halo-effect.
You seen it?
Yes
-Of course-
The brain is like that, it's electromegnatic field remains charged,
just briefly, even after death.
Cicruits remain open.
Now there is another curiosity about the brain.
It contains a short-term memory track that's about 8 mins long.
like a convenient store's security camera
that only records the last part of the activities of the day on his harddrive.
Now combining this two phenomena,
hardware that remains viable after death
and a memory bank that goes back 8 Minutes
Source code enables us to exploir the overlap
Sean Fentress died on this train, of all the passengers
aboard he was your best link.
you two share the compatibility in terms of gender,
body-size and your synaptic maps.
What happens after the 8 minutes?
-After, nothing-
you cease to exist on the train.
You can't  exist inside the source code, beyond Fentresse's 8 minutes...
Source Code is not time travel...
Source Code is time-reassignment.
It gives us access to a parallel reality.
Now the deaths on the train were a tragedy
, but source code
enpowers us...
-But I saved....-
one person.
That girl, that's always sitting across of me.
I pulled her off the train.
Give me her name.
Christina, I don't remember her last name.
Her name is Christina Warren
-Yes!-
She was 28
-That's her-
born in Illionois
Died this morning on the train.
No, I pulled her off.
She's fine.
No, she isn't.
-Believe me, she is-
She saw me get hit by the express train.
This isn't getting us anywere.
We have to send him in again. A second attack is imminent, Dr. Brudlegde.
What second attack?
-The train was just the beginning-
A letter of intent.
-I am sorry, what are you telling me here?-
we have information that downton Chicago is the next target
And they're planning to detonate a dirty bomb.
You have any idea how many people would die if
that bomb detonates in the city?
We're evacuating as we speak.
We've to stop that this happens, do you understand?
If you find the bomber, his second attack, his real attack, we think, can be prevented.
We have very little time left.
Up here the clocks are only moving in one direction.
Charge the drivers.
On the upper deck of the next carriage
there is a conductor's compartment.
It's a small office containing a safe.
Inside is a loaded handgun.Get to it.
You are authorized to use whatever force necessary.
You're still here.
-Of course I am-
Guess what.
You've quit your job and signed to a law course.
Good guess.
spilled coffee
Listen to me...
Don't answer that, you deserve better than that guy.
Everything looks better in retrospect, doesn't?
How did you know there was
How well do you know me?
-Not that well apparently-
You know me well enough, that you would trust me, if
I am acting a little bit strange or even dangerous, would you do that?
No
Wow, that was honest.
You are beatiful, you're kind,
and you are painfully honest
Who are you and what did you do to Sean Fentress?
-It's the new me-
I don't want to hurt you.
No I am not gonna sit in my seat.
He is bleeding, he needs medical attention.
Is it true, you tried to steal a gun out
of the train security box?
Careful ma'm!
What were you thinking?
-Can I borrow your phone?
No, you need to go to the hospital,  Sean.
-Please, I need your phone!-
-
You need help, NO,
why do you want my phone?
What would you do if you had only one minute left to live?
-I don't know-
I would call my dad, I wonna hear his voice
and then tell him, I am sorry
Tell me everything is gonna be ok.
-Everything is gonna be ok-
Oh yea, the gun in the strongbox, that was a
really great idea. Thanks for that.
Did you make any progress?
-Can I get access to a phone?-
I need to talk to my father.
I will try to work on that soon.
Yes, I will try....
Goodwin, how I am doing?
I am just trying to measure my performance here.
have you ever gotten back in?
I am doing any better than you did?
No, we're wasting valueble time here.
No, no, I had never been on the other side
of a source code mission. I wouldn't be viable candidate for it.
Why not?
(CAOC-N, what is that?)
Because the specifactions are extremely narrow.
What are they?
Captain, you should have found the suspect by now.
This tactical advantage, this termendous tool we've given you.
Don't waste it by thinking.
Do.
Please contact my father for me.
This will stop at some point, captain.
as soon you finish the mission.
And you doing really great. This will end.
Whoever planted the bomb, had equipment of some kind.
Gloves, screw-driver, flashlight, something....
Check bags, backpacks, briefcases, anything.
So...I took your advice.
very good advice.
What are you doing?
-I am just...-
trying to rember something
What is that?
-It's a military patch-
were you in the military?
A friend of mine was
He was in afghanistan and he disappeared and no one
heared from him since.
Do you have Internet on your phone?
No it's just connacted to the office
by a really long piece of string.
Do you think, you can see what you can find
on this guys?
He has been on my mind a lot lately,
His name is Captain Colter Stevens,
he is in the 17th airborn.
Ok you owe me.
I'll buy you a cup of coffee...
-I get one for you now-
Christina
Ehmm, I been having this dreams lately...
really vivid
and you been in them?
-really?-
What...no...
No that I wouldn't its just...
I call you back in a minute honey.
Learning?
-Yea-
For what?
Ehh, psychology..
I got a big test this morning, so I should get back to it
Can I borrow your pen?
-Yea, sure-
Hey, that's not cool man.
The bag is a mess.
-What you doing man?-
never find what I am looking for,
just like my bag.
How about you let the guy have his bag back?
-Finish your deal!-
Stay out of this tough guy
or doesn't end well for you.
You can't do that.
Dick.
(Walter Reed military center)
Excuse me, ma',m. How you doing, good morning.
You working at Walter Reed?
Yea, I used to.
Ehm,
I am in the military.
-You are in the military?-
Yea I am.
-I mean, what was going on down there?-
Oh you know, but we were a little
argument about this patch.
Is that what they train you to do? Assault civilians?
-Ma'm please do any of these letter come familiar to you?
do you know what the "n" stands for?
-It's airforce, and the "n" stand for nellis-