Uploaded by Sahos from Subscene.com/Yify-torrents.com
It's me, Peter Parker.
Your friendly neighborhood...
... you know.
I've come a long way from being
the boy who was bit by a spider.
Back then, nothing seemed
to go right for me. Now...
Wow, look, it's Spider-Man!
- Super cool!
- Spider-man!
... people really like me.
Stick around. It's gonna start again
in a couple minutes.
That's okay.
The city is safe and sound.
I guess I've had something
to do with that.
My Uncle Ben would be proud.
I still get to school. Top of my class.
Now, the Hamiltonian shows us...
...that the energy levels
are perturbed by the electric field.
From the form of this matrix,
we can see?
Miss Stacy?
That only the "m equals zero
quantum states" are affected.
Correct. Good work, Miss Stacy.
Parker? You got something to add?
No, sir.
And I'm in love
with the girl of my dreams.
Hi.
Miss Watson left a ticket for me.
Peter Parker.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Thank you. Sorry.
I'm so nervous.
That's my girlfriend.
- I thought she was good.
- Yeah.
Harry?
Harry!
I need to talk to you.
Explain things.
Tell it to my father.
Raise him from the dead.
I'm your friend, Harry.
I cared about your father.
M. J!
- Peter!
- Congrats!
- Was I good?
- Good? You were great.
- You were...
- You said great.
I love my flowers, they're beautiful.
And those are from Harry.
- Was he here tonight?
- Yeah, I ran into him outside.
- What's with you guys anyway?
- It's complicated.
Tell me again. Was I really good?
I was so nervous.
My knees were shaking.
- Your knees were fine.
- The applause wasn't very loud.
Yes, it was. Well, it's the acoustics.
It's all about diffusion. It keeps
the sound waves from grouping.
When the sound waves,
they propagate, then it's like an...
You are such a nerd.
Did you see that one?
You know what?
I'd like to sing on-stage
for the rest of my life...
...with you in the first row.
I'll be there.
Tell me you love me.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I always have.
- Ready?
- Yep.
You can't hide here, Flint.
- I'm just here to see my daughter.
- You are an escaped convict.
The cops are looking for you.
You're not getting near her.
You're nothing but a common thief.
- You maybe even killed a man?
- It wasn't like that.
It wasn't.
I had good reason
for what I was doing.
And that's the truth.
You and the truth, sitting in prison,
having three meals a day together.
I live in the presence of great truth...
...and that is the truth
that you left behind...
...right there in that bedroom.
Penny.
I missed you.
I miss you too, Daddy.
I promise I'll make you healthy again.
Whatever it takes, I'll get the money.
You get out of here. Now.
I'm not a bad person.
Just had bad luck.
Peter, what is it?
It's M. J.
- I'm gonna ask her to marry me.
- Oh, Peter.
The day your Uncle Ben asked me
to marry him, we were so scared.
And excited.
And very young.
And I loved him so fiercely.
- And you said yes, right?
- No.
I wanted to say yes, but I said no.
I wasn't ready. Neither was he.
So we took our time.
Looked forward to it.
Didn't want to run into something
with nothing to count on but love.
A man has to be understanding...
...and put his wife before himself.
Can you do that, Peter?
Yeah, I think I can.
Then you have my blessing.
I hope you've considered
a proper proposal.
Your uncle had it all planned.
He took me to the beach
one Sunday.
Oh, he was a knockout
in his bathing suit.
And I didn't look too bad myself.
We were very good swimmers.
And it was a beautiful day
and he said:
"Let's swim to the island."
And at the island, we found
a perfect spot by an old tree...
...and we lay down
and looked up at the sky.
And then he said,
"Close your eyes, May."
And I did.
And then he said, "Open them."
And he was holding this ring.
Dazzling...
...in front of me.
I thought it was the sun.
We'd be married 50 years...
...come August if...
So...
...I hope you'll make it very special
for Mary Jane.
Do something she'll never forget.
Give her this.
Go on. Take it.
- Harry.
- You knew this was coming, Pete.
Listen to me. I didn't kill your father.
He was trying to kill me.
He killed himself.
Shut up!
I'm still here, Peter.
Hate those things.
Harry?
Harry.
Oh, my God.
Harry!
Come on!
God.
- Defib.
- Two hundred.
And clear.
No response.
- Recharge, let's go again.
- Go ahead.
- Charging.
- And clear.
No response.
Let's recharge and do it
one more time. And clear.
Captain Stacy.
- What's this?
- Flint Marko.
The guy we tied
to the Ben Parker homicide.
- What about him?
- Broke out of Rikers.
- And?
- He's on the run.
He's in the marshlands.
I think we got him.
There he is.
You two, take the west side.
Tommy, take the east.
Where did he go?
- Capacitors charged.
- Right.
Donnie, we got a little fluctuation
on one.
- There's a change in the silicon mass.
- It's probably a bird. It'll fly away.
Initiating demolecularization.
- How is he?
- He's gonna be okay.
But there's been
some memory impairment.
Particularly his short-term memory.
Right now he can't
remember the accident...
...or anything that happened
to him recently.
Is it permanent?
It could be. Only time will tell.
He's awake if you wanna see him.
Maybe I should wait.
No, it's fine. Just keep it brief.
I want him to rest.
Hey, buddy.
Hey.
Hit my head.
Yeah.
Doctor said I was in an accident.
Hit-and-run.
I don't remember much of anything.
My father...
...he died, right?
This is all so weird.
Hi. I got here as fast as I could.
I know that face.
How you doing?
I don't know.
Last thing I remember, I was fine.
Somewhere.
You're still fine.
We love you, Harry.
It feels like...
...somehow I've been gone
for a really long time.
And now I'm back home.
It's good to have you back.
I'm sorry, I'm gonna have to ask
you guys to scoot, okay?
- Okay.
- All right. Thank you.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah. Great.
Get some sleep.
- I think he's gonna be fine.
- I think so.
- And you guys seem great.
- Yeah.
You have lovely friends.
My best friends.
I'd give my life for them.
- Yeah?
- It's me.
Hey.
Peter, you know I can't open the door.
It's stuck again?
Just come on and help me.
I'm coming.
- Hey.
- The review.
- They hated it. They hated me.
- Well, they can't hate you.
"The young Miss Watson
is a pretty girl...
...easy on the eyes,
but not on the ears.
Her small voice didn't carry
past the first row."
That's ridiculous, I was right there.
You were in the first row.
Yeah, this... Listen, you were great.
That's a critic. This is something
you're gonna have to get used to.
Believe me, I know.
Spider-Man gets attacked all the time.
This isn't about you. This is about me.
It's about my career.
I know, and I'm just saying
you can't let it bring you down.
You gotta believe in yourself
and pull yourself together.
You get right back
on the horse and...
Don't give me the horse thing.
Try and understand how I feel.
It's just...
...I look at these words...
...and it's like my father wrote them.
All cars. All cars in the vicinity of
54th and Sixth Avenue, please report.
Crane out of control,
approach with caution.
"Go get them, tiger"?
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God. 7-Adam to Central.
That crane job you sent us on?
It's bigger than we thought.
We're gonna need
a major mobilization right away.
Shut it down at the generator. Now!
Okay, Gwen, I've got a secret:
It's my copier.
What is that thing
doing in my background?
They got some kind of short.
Can't shut down the crane.
Get Edison on the phone.
Kill the power to the whole block.
Are you all right?
It's coming back.
Oh, no.
- Oh, my God. That's Gwen.
- What?
What's she doing up there?
I just saw her last night.
She said she had a modeling gig.
- Who are you?
- It's Brock, sir. Edward Brock Jr.
And I work at the Daily Bugle.
And I'm dating your daughter.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Thank you.
Hey, Spidey, hold on.
Bugle needs a photo.
- Thank God you're okay.
- Daddy.
Hey. I'm the new guy.
New guy?
You okay?
From now on, I am gonna be
taking shots of you for the Bugle.
So smile. Are you smiling?
Just kidding.
- They got a guy.
- Who, Parker?
Yeah, look, just between you and me,
guy's kind of an amateur.
Have you noticed his stuff
makes you look a little bloated?
Just... Yeah, a little chunky.
Okay.
But you don't have to worry about that
anymore, buddy.
Dazzle me.
Just something the boys in
the Ad Department and I whipped up.
As you know, circulation at the Bugle's
been pretty good.
Though not as good
as The New York Times.
Or the Daily News, or the Post,
or several other smaller...
Get on with it, you moron...!
- What?
- Your blood pressure, Mr. Jameson.
- Your wife told you to watch the anger.
- You tell my wife...
Thank you.
So I propose this campaign.
''Daily Bugle. " That's obvious.
"It's hip, it's now."
I came up with that one.
"It's wow." That's actually Erickson.
He goes crazy.
We gave him a couple lattes,
it's like:
"And how." That's me again.
Time to take your pill.
Not that one.
Drink plenty of water.
Thank you.
Continue.
- He's busy.
- I'm just here to talk to you, beautiful.
What's that smell?
That's a little something called
Nice and Easy. What's on you?
It's called Go Away.
That is the dumbest idea
you've ever had...
...and you have had some doozies.
- Blood pressure.
Hey, where are you going?
- Who are you?
- You hired him last week. Freelance.
- I did? What's that smell?
- It's Brock, sir. Edward Brock Jr.
Can I just say I really like that shirt?
It's the crane accident.
- Check out the light.
- He likes my shirt.
- Hey, Betty.
- Hey, Pete.
You better get in there. New guy.
He's trying to sell
some Spidey photos.
Thanks.
Parker. You're late, maybe too late.
Bruckner beat you to it.
It's Brock, sir. Edward Brock Jr.
- But I got you this.
- But he got me this.
I didn't see you there.
How'd you get that high?
- Climbed. Nearly fell off a flagpole.
- A flagpole?