The Tesseract has awakened.
It is on a little world, a human world.
They would wield its power,
but our ally knows its
workings as they never will.
He is ready to lead
and our force, our Chitauri, will follow.
A world will be his.
The universe, yours.
And the humans,
what can they do but burn?
All personnel,
the evacuation order
has been confirmed.
How bad is it?
That's the problem, sir. We don't know.
Dr Selvig read an energy surge
from the Tesseract four hours ago.
NASA didn't authorise Selvig
to go to test phase.
He wasn't testing it.
He wasn't even in the room.
Spontaneous event.
It just turned itself on?
Where are the energy levels now?
Climbing. When Selvig couldn't
shut it down, we ordered evac.
How long to get everyone out?
Campus should be clear
in the next half-hour.
Do better.
Sir, evacuation may be futile.
We should tell them
to go back to sleep?
If we can't control
the Tesseract's energy,
there may not be
a minimum safe distance.
I need you to make sure
the Phase 2 prototypes
are shipped out.
Sir, is that really a priority right now?
Until such time as the world ends,
we will act as though
it intends to spin on.
Clear out the tech below.
Every piece of Phase 2
on a truck and gone.
Yes, sir.
With me.
Talk to me, Doctor.
Director.
Is there anything we know for certain?
The Tesseract is misbehaving.
- Is that supposed to be funny?
- No, it's not funny at all.
The Tesseract is not only
active, she's behaving.
I assume you pulled the plug.
She's an energy source.
We turn off the power,
she turns it back on.
If she reaches peak level...
We prepared for this, Doctor.
Harnessing energy from space.
But we don't have the harness.
My calculations are far from complete.
And she's throwing off
interference, radiation.
Nothing harmful,
low levels of gamma radiation.
That can be harmful.
Where's Agent Barton?
The Hawk?
Up in his nest, as usual.
Agent Barton, report.
I gave you this detail
so you could keep
a close eye on things.
Well, I see better from a distance.